[
    {
      "id": "q1",
      "question": "Who is the main protagonist for Final Fantasy XVI?",
      "answers": [
        "Cloud Strife",
        "Squall Leonhart",
        "Clive Rosfield",
        "Boggeyman"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Clive Rosfield"
    },
    {
      "id": "q2",
      "question": "Which of the following is not considered a summon in Crisis  Core: Final Fantasy VII?",
      "answers": ["Bahamut", "Odin", "Ifrit", "Shinryu"],
      "correctAnswer": "Shinryu"
    },
    {
      "id": "q3",
      "question": "In Dissidia 012 Duodecim, they included both the main protagonist and antagonist from the mainline games. Which mainline game did not include an antagonist?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy XIII",
        "Final Fantasy X",
        "Final Fantasy VI",
        "Final Fantasy VIII"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy XIII"
    },
    {
      "id": "q4",
      "question": "In which game is 'Cloud Strife' playable in?",
      "answers": [
        "Crisis Core: Final Fantasy VII",
        "Dissidia: Final Fantasy",
        "Dirge of Cerberus: Final Fantasy VII",
        "Before Crisis: Final Fantasy VII"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Dissidia: Final Fantasy"
    },
    {
      "id": "q5",
      "question": "Which of the following is considered an MMORPG (Massive Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game)?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy XIV",
        "Final Fantasy XVI",
        "Final Fantasy XII",
        "Final Fantasy XV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy XIV"
    },
    {
      "id": "q6",
      "question": "Bahamut makes an appearance (Eikon, Primal, Summon, etc) in many games. In which game was it's first appearace?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy I",
        "Final Fantasy VI",
        "Final Fantasy XI",
        "Final Fantasy XIV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy I"
    },
    {
      "id": "q7",
      "question": "Which game was first introduced into the 3D gaming era?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy V",
        "Final Fantasy VI",
        "Final Fantasy VII",
        "Final Fantasy VIII"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy VII"
    },
    {
      "id": "q8",
      "question": "Many games had many different crossovers. Which of the following did not include Final Fantasy content?",
      "answers": [
        "Phantasy Star Online 2",
        "Monster Hunter World",
        "Super Smash Bros. Ultimate",
        "Nier Automata"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nier Automata"
    },
    {
      "id": "q9",
      "question": "Who is the main protagonist for Final Fantasy VI?",
      "answers": [
        "Terra Branford",
        "Cecil Harvey",
        "Jill Valentine",
        "Bartz Klauser"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Terra Branford"
    },
    {
      "id": "q10",
      "question": "Which was the first Final Fantasy game released on a non-Nintendo system?",
      "answers": ["Sega Genesis", "Sony Playstation", "Phillips CDI", "Xbox"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sony Playstation"
    },
    {
      "id": "q11",
      "question": "Which game first introduced chocobos?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy I",
        "Final Fantasy II",
        "Final Fantasy III",
        "Final Fantasy IV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy II"
    },
    {
      "id": "q12",
      "question": "There's a character that travels the void to visit the other series of the game. Which character does this?",
      "answers": ["Exdeath", "Firion", "Bahamut", "Gilgamesh"],
      "correctAnswer": "Gilgamesh"
    },
    {
      "id": "q13",
      "question": "Triple Triad is a card game from Final Fantasy. Which game was it first introduced in?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy III",
        "Final Fantasy V",
        "Final Fantasy VIII",
        "Final Fantasy XIV"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy VIII"
    },
    {
      "id": "q14",
      "question": "Which Japanese Final Fantasy game was released as 'Final Fantasy II' in America?",
      "answers": ["Final Fantasy II", "Final Fantasy IV", "Final Fantasy III", "Final Fantasy V"],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy II"
    },
    {
      "id": "q15",
      "question": "What is the name of the monster race with pom-poms on their heads and their catchphrase is 'Kupo!'?",
      "answers": ["Chocobos", "Goblins", "Moogles", "Typhon"],
      "correctAnswer": "Moogles"
    },
    {
      "id": "q16",
      "question": "Final Fantasy introduced a monster that's basically a ball of fire and causes explosion. What is the monster's name?",
      "answers": ["Bombs", "Grenades", "Mines", "Missles"],
      "correctAnswer": "Bombs"
    },
    {
      "id": "q17",
      "question": "Which mainline Final Fantasy was first introduced as an MMORPG (Massive Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game)?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy V",
        "Final Fantasy XI",
        "Final Fantasy XIV",
        "Final Fantasy XVI"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy XI"
    },
    {
      "id": "q18",
      "question": "In what year was the first Final Fantasy game officially released in North America?",
      "answers": [
        "1987",
        "1990",
        "1988",
        "1991"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1990"
    },
    {
      "id": "q19",
      "question": "Final Fantasy is known to re-release remaster/remakes of the previous games. Besides the new recent game, which mainline Final Fantasy did not get released?",
      "answers": [
        "Final Fantasy III",
        "Final Fantasy XIII",
        "Final Fantasy VIII",
        "Final Fantasy XI"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Final Fantasy XI"
    },
    {
      "id": "q20",
      "question": "Final Fantasy is known to create very memorial music throughout the years. Who is the main composer that keeps creating the magic of Final Fantasy music?",
      "answers": [
        "Koji Kondo",
        "Nobuo Uematsu",
        "Noctis Lucis Caelum",
        "Yoko Taro"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Nobuo Uematsu"
    }
  ]
  